Five, six common tests that we essentially go over.
And this is all going to be how their athleticism is expressed and how we can get measurements
around them.
So number one, we test out their speed.
So this is typically a 10-yard dash to be able to test out their acceleration, or you
can just simply do like an overall 40-yard dash, something of that nature, to be able
to get obviously both acceleration and top speed.
Number two is going to be kind of more on the agility side.
So it's obviously predetermined, but we do a pro shuttle.
So your basic five, 10, five.
We want to be able to see how they redirect force, decelerate, and accelerate.
Number three is going to be their power.
We do a vertical jump.
Then the second one is going to be their horizontal force, which is going to be a standard broad
jump.
Then the other aspect of power that we do test out is going to be their single leg broad.
After we've gone through off-season training program, whether it be 60 or 90 days, we then
retest those basic dynamic speed and power movements.
And then the training should have done the work to be able to see those numbers increase.
Five, six, common.